linkdex.com 2016-06-22

# Find out about our privacy policy | Linkdex (US)

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

This document should be read in conjunction with our [terms](http://www.linkdex.com/en-us/terms/) of use, which outlines key terminology and Service policies.

It should be noted that this Website serves an international audience, and so elements of this policy may be more (or less) relevant to specific audiences based on territory and legal jurisdictions.

## 1\. Information Collection

We collect information about you:

  * that you provide by filling in forms on this site, such as your name, email address, phone number, company name or other details we need in order to help you with your experience
  * This includes information which you provide when registering to use the Linkdex SEO Service.
  * if you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence; when you visit this site (see also under Cookies below).
  * By using our site you are giving us permission to use your personal information in the ways set out in this Privacy Policy.

## 2\. Use of your information

We use your information to provide our services to you and to support your relationship with us, and, if you agree, to send you information about other services we think may be of interest to you. Additionally, we may use it to:

  * Personalize user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products, services, promotions and events which may be of interest to you (You can opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us at any time by contacting us at [support@linkdex.com](mailto:support@linkdex.com)).
  * To personalise your repeat visits to this site.

## 3\. How do we protect visitor information?

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is Linkdex Limited. Linkdex is registered under the Act under registration number: PZ2610422.

## 4\. Google

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users, and can be found here: <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

We have implemented the following:

  * Demographics and Interests Reporting
  * DoubleClick Platform Integration

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

### Opting out

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

## 5\. California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at: <http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf>

### According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:

  * Users can visit our site anonymously
  * Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on our Privacy Policy page
  * Users are able to change their personal information by emailing us at [support@linkdex.com](mailto:support@linkdex.com)

## 6\. COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the USA’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

## 7\. Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach relating to personal information occur, We will notify the users via email within 7 business days.

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

## 8\. CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred

To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:

  * NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
  * Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link within each email

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at [support@linkdex.com](mailto:support@linkdex.com)  
and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

## 9\. Disclosure of your information

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our corporate group. We may also disclose your personal information to certain third parties in the following scenarios:

  * If we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;
  * if Linkdex Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal information held by it about its users and customers will be one of the transferred assets;
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Linkdex Limited, our customers, or others.

## 10\. Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## 11\. Cookies

Like many websites we use cookies to store and then retrieve small bits of information on your computer when you visit. This information is used to make the site work as you expect it to. It is not personally identifiable to you, but it can be used to give you a more personalised web experience.

Some of the information stored is put there by other companies whose software we have added to the site, and this can also impact your experience of other websites you may visit after leaving ours.

If you continue to use this site without taking action to prevent the storage of this information, you are effectively agreeing to this use.

If you want to learn more about the general uses of cookies, including how to stop them being stored by your computer, please visit [Cookiepedia – all about cookies](http://cookiepedia.co.uk/all-about-cookies).

Below is a list of the different types of cookies used on this site, and an explanation of what they are used for. If you would like any more information, please get in touch.

### Strictly Necessary Cookies

These cookies are necessary for the website to function. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a request for services, such as logging in or filling in forms.

You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of the site will not then work. These cookies do not store any personally identifiable information.

### Performance Cookies

These cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site.

All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. If you do not allow these cookies we will not know when you have visited our site, and will not be able to monitor its performance.

### Functionality Cookies

These cookies enable the website to provide enhanced functionality and personalisation. They may be set by us or by third party providers whose services we have added to our pages.

If you do not allow these cookies then some or all of these services may not function properly.

### Targeting Cookies

These cookies may be set through our site by our advertising partners. They may be used by those companies to build a profile of your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites.

They do not store any personally identifiable information, but are based on uniquely identifying your browser and internet device. If you do not allow these cookies, you will experience less targeted advertising.

### Other Cookies

The following cookies are also set by our site, however their purpose has not yet been identified. We are conducting research into these cookies and will update this page as soon as possible.
